⦅知ってますか？
Did you know?
The distance from your eye level to the horizon
人の目の高さから見える
水平線までの距離は
約４ｷﾛﾒｰﾄﾙなんですよ｡
is around four kilometers.
Do the people who live around here
have a habit of talking to total strangers?
(咲太)このへんの人って
見ず知らずの人に
突然 話しかけたり
するもんなんですか？
あっ もしかして 私のこと
ﾍﾝな人だと思ってます？
Wait, do you think I'm some weirdo?
Nah, I just think you're annoying.
いえ ｳｻﾞい人だと
思ってるだけです｡
You can't say that to a high school girl.
それ 女子高生には禁句です｡
There are three taboo words:
annoying, clueless, and lame.
ｳｻﾞい ﾀﾞｻい 空気読めないは
三大禁句｡
少年は ずいぶんと
やさぐれているようですけど
You seem to have lost your way, kiddo.
Did something bad happen?
何か嫌なことでも
あったんですか？
私は 牧之原翔子です｡
I'm Makinohara Shouko.
牧之原ｻｰﾋﾞｽｴﾘｱの牧之原に
大空を翔る子の翔子｡
Shouko with the character for flying, like in the sky,
and Makinohara from "Makinohara Service Area."
少年の名前は？⦆
What's your name?
Good morning, Onii-chan.
(かえで)おはようございます
お兄ちゃん｡
Kaede, how many times must I tell you
to quit sneaking into my bed?
かえで 何度も言ってるが
僕のﾍﾞｯﾄﾞに潜り込むのは
やめなさい｡
Why? Because you might awaken to a forbidden love?
お兄ちゃんが禁断の愛に
目覚めてしまうからですか？
Hell no. It's just warm enough already
without you in there.
違うな ただただ暑いから
やめてほしいんだ｡
August 2nd
The girl who appeared before me that day
along with the abandoned cat
《あの日 捨て猫と一緒に
僕の前に現れた少女は
僕が２年前に出会った
had the same name as my first love,
the high school girl I met two years ago.
初恋相手の女子高生と
同じ名前だった》
My name is Makinohara Shouko.
⦅牧之原翔子といいます⦆
She had the same name...
《同じ名前だったんだけど…》
《本人は 僕のことなど
何も知らず
but she didn't recognize me at all,
何事も起きないまま
夏休みは２週間過ぎた》
and an uneventful two weeks of summer break flew by.
There, there.
よしよし いい子にしてましたか？
はやて｡
Have you been a good boy, Hayate?
Oh...
《あっ 猫の名前は
はやてに決まった｡
The cat was named Hayate. He and Nasuno
are now Tohoku Shinkansen buddies.
なすのとは東北つながり》
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい 引き取りたいと
言っておきながら
I said I wanted to keep him, but I haven't been able to bring it up to my parents.
なかなか両親に言い出せなくて｡
It's fine. He can stay with us for the time being.
しばらくは うちで
預かっておくから 平気だよ｡
なすのも喜んでるし｡
牧之原さんも ここで
Nasuno seems to enjoy the company.
And you can practice how to take care of a cat here.
猫の世話の練習をしておけばいい｡
はい｡
Thank you.
Onii-chan, are you someone who prefers much younger little sisters?
お兄ちゃんは 妹は若い子のほうが
いい人ですか？
清楚で礼儀正しい妹が
Do you prefer refined and
well-mannered little sisters?
What's with those questions?
なんだ その質問は｡
今 かえでは
I'm currently facing the crisis of a lifetime!
かえで史上最大のﾋﾟﾝﾁなんです｡
I need to master the way of the
little sister as quickly as possible!
１日も早く 妹道を
極めないといけないんです｡
I'm someone who's perfectly content with having you as my little sister.
僕は 妹は かえで１人いれば
いい人だな｡
Th-Then...
で では 翔子さんは
お兄ちゃんにとって
What is Shouko-san to you?
何なんですか？
何なんだろうな｡
What, indeed?
牧之原さん お姉さんは
いないんだよね？
Makinohara-san, you don't have an older sister, right?
はい 一人っ子ですから｡
That's right. I'm an only child.
Any cousins who look a lot like you?
親戚に よく似た人は？
いないと思います｡
I don't think so.
ﾊｧ… やっぱり
双葉に相談しとくかな｡
I guess I really should talk to Futaba about this.
Azusagawa
What is it, Azusagawa?
(理央)なに？ 梓川｡
Episode 7: Youth Is a Paradox
Futaba?
双葉？
髪おろしてると暑いんだよ｡
It's too hot to wear my hair down.
ﾒｶﾞﾈをしてないのはｺﾝﾀｸﾄだから｡
And I'm wearing contacts, so no glasses.
なんで制服？
このあと学校｡
Why the uniform?
I'm on my way to school.
国見なら ﾊﾞｲﾄだからいないぞ｡
Kunimi won't be there. He's got work.
部員１人の科学部は
活動実績を残しておかないと
I'm the only member of the science club.
It'll be shut down if I'm not productive.
即廃部になるんだよ｡
So, what did you want to talk about?
で 梓川の用事っていうのは？
あ ああ…｡
O-Oh, the thing is...
実は… 牧之原翔子に会った｡
I met Makinohara Shouko.
Your first love? She was real, huh?
梓川の初恋の人？
実在したんだ｡
Shockingly, she'd turned into a middle-school first-year.
しかも 驚いたことに
中学１年生になってた｡
Have you lost your mind?
梓川 正気？
残念ながら｡
Unfortunately not.
よく似た同姓同名の
別人なんじゃないの？
It must be a different girl who just looks like her
and has the same name.
I hear everyone in the world has two doppelgangers.
世界には 同じ顔をした人間が
３人いるらしいよ｡
That's just a common myth.
んなの よくある都市伝説だろ｡
そうだね よくある都市伝説…｡
Yeah, just a common myth.
でもさ 今のところ そっちは
実害ないんでしょ？
Anyway, no harm's been done so far, right?
I guess not.
まあ ないな｡
だったら いいんじゃない？
Then don't worry about it.
Oh, is there a fireworks show happening somewhere?
今日 どっかで花火やるんだな｡
Tonight, at Chigasaki.
茅ヶ崎が今日｡
そういや 去年 行ったよな
花火大会 国見と３人で｡
That reminds me, we went to one with Kunimi last year.
あのとき 双葉 私服だったよな
浴衣 着てくればよかったのに｡
And you dressed normally for it.
You should've worn a yukata.
どうして 私が梓川のために
Why should I have to wear one for you?
They're a massive pain.
そんな面倒なことを
しなくちゃいけないわけ？
国見に見せるためだよ｡
どのみち 私には似合わない｡
To show Kunimi.
I wouldn't look good in one, anyway.
浴衣って 胸が大きいと
ﾀﾞﾒなんだっけ？
Does a yukata not go well with big boobs?
That's not what I meant.
そういう意味で言ったんじゃない｡
今の髪型で浴衣着たら
I think it'd go pretty great with that hairstyle.
かなりいいと思うけどな｡
Forget it.
もういい 梓川はﾊﾞｲﾄでしょ
それじゃ｡
You have work, right? See you.
Thanks for hearing me out.
相談のってくれてｻﾝｷｭ｡
Did you get even more of a tan?
お前 更に日焼けしてないか？
(国見)おととい
海に行ったせいかも｡
I hit the beach the day before yesterday.
上里と？
そうだけど｡
With Kamisato?
Yeah, why?
God, so annoying.
ｳﾍｯ ｳｻﾞいな｡
Hey, you have a ridiculously hot girlfriend too.
咲太だって とんでもなく美人な
彼女がいるだろ｡
One I haven't seen in a week
because she's ridiculously busy.
その麻衣さんは
とんでもなく忙しくて
この１週間 顔を見てない｡
俺 昨日 ﾃﾚﾋﾞで見たぞ｡
I saw her on TV yesterday.
Rest assured, I see her every day on the TV too.
安心しろ ﾃﾚﾋﾞでなら
僕も毎日見てる｡
Hello...
(朋絵)おはようございます…｡
Ack, Senpai!
ｹﾞｯ 先輩！
かわいい浴衣を
Did you come to show off your cute yukata?
自慢しにきたのか？
来週の予定出してないから
I'm just here to submit my
shift request for next week.
出しにきただけだし｡
I must admit, you look nice in one.
古賀って 浴衣似合うのな｡
今 胸見て言ったでしょ｡
Did you say that after looking at my chest?
腰とお尻のﾊﾞﾗﾝｽも含めたうえでの
発言だ｡
I also took your waist and butt into account before making the observation.
ﾊﾞﾘﾑｶ～！ どうせ 帯に
どっかり乗るような
Now I'm steamin'!
Yeah, yeah, I don't have boobs big enough
to hang over the sash!
立派な胸はないですよ！
寸胴ですよ！
And my waist isn't shapely!
いらっしゃいま…｡
Welcome—
ﾛｹから帰ってくるの
明日でしたよね？
Weren't you only supposed to come back
from the shoot tomorrow?
(麻衣)ﾍﾞﾃﾗﾝの役者が
多い現場だったし
There were a lot of veteran actors,
私もNG出さないから
早く終わったのよ｡
and I don't need many retakes,
so it ended sooner than expected.
なるほど で １日でも早く
僕に会いたくて
I see.
And you rushed back because you wanted to see me as soon as possible?
帰ってきたんですね｡
うれしいなぁ｡
I'm so chuffed.
なによ それ｡
What's with that tone?
お決まりでしたら
ご注文をどうぞ｡
If you've decided on your order, I'll take it.
ん…｡
ご注文をどうぞ｡
I'll take your order.
なに すねてるのよ｡
すねてません｡
What are you sulking for?
I'm not sulking.
You clearly are.
すねてるじゃない｡
誰のせいだと思いますか？
Whose fault do you think that is?
それは その…｡
その？
Uh, well...
Well?
ごめん…｡
Sorry.
仕事に夢中で
つきあって間もない彼氏を
I'm aware I'm being an awful girlfriend
who's neglecting her new boyfriend due to work.
ほったらかしにしている
ひどい彼女だってことは
自覚してる｡
そこまでは思ってないけど…｡
Hey, I don't think you're "awful," but...
けど？
お詫びには期待してます｡
But?
I do expect you to make up for this.
わかった それなりのことは
してあげるから｡
Fine. I'll do something nice for you.
ｴﾛいことでも？
少しくらいならね｡
Even if it's lewd?
A little bit.
じゃあ 許してあげます｡
調子にのるな｡
I'll forgive you, then.
Don't push your luck.
I'm overjoyed that you came back so early!
早く帰ってきてくれて
すげえうれしいです｡
You should've said that first, stupid.
ﾊﾞｰｶ それを先に言いなさい｡
ﾊﾞｲﾄ何時まで？ 待っててあげる｡
When does your shift end? I'll wait.
彼女 毎日来てるの？
ん？
Has she been coming every day?
咲太の初恋相手にｿｯｸﾘな
牧之原翔子さん｡
Makinohara Shouko, the girl who looks just like your first love.
来てますよ 気になります？
She has. Does it bother you?
Why would I feel threatened
by a middle-school first-year?
中学１年生の女の子相手に
嫉妬なんてするわけないでしょ｡
何か変わったことは？
ないですね｡
Anything unusual happen?
Not really.
何かわかったことは？
Figure anything out?
I even talked to Futaba about it, but not a thing.
双葉にも相談してみたんですけど
何にも｡
そんな話より 僕は麻衣さんと
もっとｲﾁｬｲﾁｬしたいなぁ｡
Rather than talk about that,
I wanna be all lovey-dovey with you.
せっかく久しぶりに会えたのに｡
We haven't seen each other in a while.
あとで好きなだけしてあげるから｡
We can be as lovey-dovey as you want later.
What? I'd rather start now.
え～ 今がいいなぁ｡
あっ あれ 双葉さんじゃない？
Hey, isn't that Futaba-san?
こんなとこで何してんだ あいつ？
What is she doing here?
I've never been in a net café before.
私 ﾈｯﾄｶﾌｪって初めて｡
これじゃ どこだか
わからないわね｡
We can't find her like this.
麻衣さん ｽﾏﾎ貸して｡
Let me borrow your phone, Mai-san.
Hello?
[℡](理央)はい｡
双葉 僕だ｡
Futaba, it's me.
Why are you calling me from a cell phone?
[℡]なんで 梓川が
ｹｰﾀｲの番号からかけてくるわけ？
麻衣さんに借りてる｡
[℡]のろけなら よそでやって｡
I'm using Mai-san's.
If you want to show off, try someone else.
What is it? More trouble?
[℡]なに また厄介ごと？
双葉の中で
Am I nothing but trouble in your mind?
僕ｲｺｰﾙ厄介ごとなのか｡
咲太 あれ｡
Look, Sakuta.
Azusagawa? What's wrong?
[℡]梓川 どうかした？
悪い なんか充電切れっぽいから
また連絡する｡
Sorry, battery's running out. I'll call back.
ちょっと待て！
Wait a sec!
電話の相手は私？
ああ｡
Were you talking to me on the phone?
Yeah.
なら ごまかしは
きかないだろうね｡
Then I guess there's no hiding it.
私が２人いるんだ｡
それ どういうことだ？
There are two of me.
What's that supposed to mean?
言ったとおり ３日前から
この世界には
Exactly what I said.
There have been two Futaba Rios
since three days ago.
双葉理央が２人いる｡
Is it Puberty Syndrome?
思春期症候群ってこと？
認めたくないですけど…｡
As much as I hate to admit it.
Any idea what caused it?
心当たりは？
あれば とっくに対処してる｡
If I did, I would've dealt with it by now.
僕が昼に本屋で会ったのは
もう一人のほうか？
The one I met at the bookstore this afternoon was your counterpart, huh?
私は梓川に会ってないから
そういうことだろうね｡
I hadn't seen you today, so it must've been.
あの偽者には迷惑してる｡
That impostor is a pain in the ass.
家に居座って
生活してくれてるおかげで
Since she's squatting at my place and going about her life, I can't even go home.
私は帰るに帰れない｡
So you went to a net café?
それでﾈｯﾄｶﾌｪかよ｡
さっさと僕に連絡よこせって｡
You should've contacted me first.
麻衣さん 今日から 双葉を
うちに泊めますけど
Mai-san, I'm going to have Futaba
stay over at my place. That's okay, right?
いいですよね？
ﾀﾞﾒよ｡
え？
Nope.
Huh? But Futaba's my friend.
だって 双葉は友達ですよ？
だったら聞くけど
Then let me ask you this:
私が家に男友達を泊めるって
言ったら 咲太はOKする？
if I said I was going to let a male friend
stay with me, would you be okay with it?
あっ… 想像するのも嫌です｡
でしょ？
I don't even want to imagine that.
Right?
だから 私も一緒に泊まる｡
So I'm going to stay over too.
お兄ちゃんが また新しい女の人を
連れてきました｡
Onii-chan brought home yet another girl.
人聞きが悪いな｡
で でも かえでは妹なので
Don't make me sound like a playboy.
B-But I'm your little sister, so I'll accept everything about you, flaws and all!
そんなお兄ちゃんも
受け入れる覚悟です｡
彼女は 友達の双葉理央｡
よろしく｡
This is Futaba Rio, my friend.
Nice to meet you.
あ 梓川かえでです…｡
I-I'm Azusagawa Kaede.
This is Nasuno,
この子は なすの｡
and this one is Hayate.
こっちの子は はやてです｡
(鳴き声)
２人とも 今日から しばらく
うちに泊まるから｡
They'll both be staying with us for a while.
えっと 麻衣さんと双葉は
僕の部屋で寝て 僕は…｡
Uh...
Mai-san and Futaba can sleep in my room, and I'll...
You can sleep with me in my room, then!
それじゃ お兄ちゃんは
かえでの部屋で一緒に！
Motion denied. I'll sleep in the living room.
却下 僕はﾘﾋﾞﾝｸﾞで寝る｡
I'm going to go home and pick up some clothes.
私 いったん家に戻って
着替えとってくる｡
お風呂も ついでに
済ませてくるから｡
I'll take a bath while I'm there, too.
You can go ahead and take a bath, then, Futaba.
じゃあ 双葉 風呂 先にいいぞ｡
Just so we're clear, I'm not gonna do anything with your bath soup.
ﾊｯｷﾘ言っとくが 双葉でﾀﾞｼとった
風呂のお湯で
どうこうするつもりはないからな｡
Azusagawa...
梓川…｡
わかってくれたか？
Understand?
You needed to die the moment you said the words "bath soup."
ﾀﾞｼとか言ってる時点で死ね｡
Teenage Pig Doesn't
Dream of Bunny Girls
I'll leave a towel here.
ﾀｵﾙ 置いておくな｡
うん｡
Okay.
着替えはあるんだっけ？
あるよ｡
Do you have a change of clothes?
I do.
If you don't, you can borrow a
bunny-girl outfit or panda pajamas.
なければ ﾊﾞﾆｰｶﾞｰﾙの衣装か
ﾊﾟﾝﾀﾞのﾊﾟｼﾞｬﾏ貸すぞ｡
今 あるって言った｡
それはそうと 大丈夫か？
I just said I do.
That aside, you okay?
梓川が そこからいなくなればね｡
I will be once you go away.
よっこいしょ…｡
Hup.
どうして 風呂の外で落ち着く？
Why would you make yourself comfortable outside the bath?
That "you okay" question was about your Puberty Syndrome.
今の ｢大丈夫か？｣は
思春期症候群についてな｡
よくわからない…｡
I don't really know.
Is that all?
それだけか？
何て言わせたいの？
What do you want me to say?
Nothing. I just want to hear what you think.
べつに
双葉の感想を聞きたいだけ｡
少し怖い…｡
I'm a little scared.
Just a little, huh?
少しだけか｡
ﾈｯﾄｶﾌｪに１人のときは
I was really scared when I was alone at the net café.
すごく怖かった｡
けどさ
But, hey, how is this even possible?
こんなことってありえるのか？
How can there be two of one person?
１人の人間が
２人存在するなんて｡
If quantum teleportation happens
on the macro level, then it is possible.
ﾏｸﾛの世界で 量子ﾃﾚﾎﾟｰﾃｰｼｮﾝが
成立するなら
可能性はあるかもね｡
Teleportation? That only happens in movies.
ﾃﾚﾎﾟｰﾃｰｼｮﾝ？
映画の話だろ それ｡
そうでもないよ 現実の話｡
ﾏｼﾞか!?
You'd be surprised. It's very real.
Seriously?
Remember how we talked
about quantum entanglement?
前に 量子もつれの話はしたよね｡
今回の件に当てはめて
簡単に説明すると
If I were to apply the theory here and explain it in simple terms...
例えば 私を構築している情報の
Let's say there's a framework of all my information, my blueprints.
設計図があるとするでしょ？
それ簡単か？
How is that simple?
その情報を
量子もつれを利用して
And that info is sent instantly,
via quantum entanglement, to a distant location.
離れた位置に
一瞬で移動させたとする｡
Like sending the info of you here, in our bath, to the school?
例えば うちの風呂にいる
双葉の情報を
学校に飛ばしたとか？
そう｡
Right.
学校にある私を構築する情報は
And if my information framework in school
誰かに観測されることで
双葉理央の姿に確定される｡
is observed by someone,
it will be recognized as Futaba Rio.
その理屈だと
同時に２人が存在するのは
Going by that logic, wouldn't it be impossible for two of you to exist at once?
無理なんじゃないのか？
そのとおりだよ｡
That's right.
実は私は もう一人の自分を
見たわけじゃないんだ｡
The thing is, I haven't actually seen my other self.
だから 同時に存在しているのかと
聞かれると
So I can't say for sure that we both exist at the same time.
そうだとは言い切れない｡
But when I saw you at the net café,
I was talking to the other one over the phone.
けど ﾈｯﾄｶﾌｪで会ったとき
僕はｽﾏﾎで もう一人の双葉と
電話をしていた｡
電話の相手は ﾎﾝﾄに私だった？
見たわけじゃないからな｡
Was it really me on the other end?
Well, I didn't see her.
あっ でも 量子ﾃﾚﾎﾟｰﾃｰｼｮﾝ？
Oh, but what was it, quantum teleportation?
双葉を構築する情報ってのが
同じなら
If both your information frameworks are the same,
どっちで観測されたとしても
wouldn't your awareness and memories be synced, no matter which of you observed it?
意識や記憶は
一緒なんじゃないのか？
私 双葉理央を観測しているのが
私自身だったとして
Let's say that I, Futaba Rio,
am being observed by myself.
私を観測する私の意識が
なんらかの理由で
Now, what if there were two of the consciousness observing me for some reason?
２つ存在しているのだとしたら
It might result in something like this current scenario.
今のような状態に
なるのかもしれない｡
You mean, like, two personas?
それって 人格が
２つあるってことか｡
仮に そうだったとして
どうして そんなことになった？
Even if that were true, why would there be two to begin with?
心当たりはないって言ったでしょ｡
Didn't I tell you I have no idea?
麻衣さん｡
ん？
Mai-san?
何してんの？
咲太の顔を見てる｡
What are you doing?
Staring at your face.
Uh, yeah, that I can tell.
いや そうなんだけど…｡
I'm staring at my boyfriend's face.
彼氏の顔を見てる｡
ﾄﾞｷｯとしたでしょ？
Heart skipped a beat, didn't it?
You're enjoying this, huh?
麻衣さん 浮かれてる？
Of course. I finally get to spend time with my boyfriend and stay over at his place.
久しぶりに彼氏とゆっくり会えて
お泊りしてるんだから
当たり前でしょ｡
双葉は？
What about Futaba?
ぐっすり眠ってる｡
Out like a light.
She probably hasn't slept in peace for days.
この何日か 安心して
眠れなかったんじゃない？
そうですか…｡
咲太は 目の前にいる私より
I see...
You're more concerned with Futaba-san when I'm right here?
双葉さんが気になるんだ｡
Aw...
あ～あ 明日
一日ｵﾌになったから
I thought I could go on a date with you tomorrow since I have the whole day off.
ﾃﾞｰﾄしてあげようと思ってたのに｡
Why are you making it sound like it's not happening?
どうしてﾀﾞﾒになった風なんですか｡
だって咲太は 双葉さんのこと
調べるつもりでしょ｡
I mean, you're going to look into Futaba-san's situation, right?
偽者は科学部の活動で
明日も学校だと思うので
The fake will probably be back at school tomorrow for science club stuff,
まあ 様子を見に行こうとは
思ってました｡
so yeah, I was thinking of going to check on her.
See? I knew it.
ほら やっぱり｡
そこで麻衣さんにお願いが｡
On that note, I need a favor from you.
嫌｡ どうせ咲太が
偽者のところに行ってる間
No.
I bet you want me to watch over Futaba-san while you're with the fake.
本物の双葉さんが どうしてるか
私に見ておけって言うんでしょ？
さすが麻衣さん
僕のこと よくわかってる｡
That's my Mai-san. You know me very well.
Don't be happy about that.
喜ぶな｡
痛い 痛い…｡
Ow. You're hurting me.
Don't be happy about that either.
喜ぶな｡
というわけなんで
So yeah, please.
お願いします｡
じゃあ 仕事が忙しくて
ほったらかしにしたお詫びは
With this, we'll be even for my
neglecting you over work, right?
ﾁｬﾗでいいわね｡
え～ お詫びはお詫びでほしいな｡
What? I need a proper token of apology!
Hey, I'm sleeping next to you right now.
今 添い寝してあげてる｡
I was hoping for something
that rhymes with "amiss."
もっとこう ねずみの鳴き声的な｡
あれ わかりませんでした？
Huh? Was that too obtuse?
You don't have use an apology as an excuse.
べつに
お詫びを理由にしなくても
時と場所と雰囲気を
ちゃんと選んでくれれば
So long as you pick the right time, place, and mood,
咲太のほうから
してくれてもいいのよ｡
I don't mind you taking the initiative, you know?
麻衣さん…｡
何よ？
Mai-san...
What?
That hurt.
痛いわね｡
麻衣さんが恥ずかしがって
It's because you got shy and tilted your head.
うつむくから｡
咲太が がっつくからよ｡
No, you went in too hard.
Mai-san?
麻衣さん？
We're done for tonight.
今日は もうおしまい｡
え～｡
Blame yourself for sucking.
咲太がﾍﾀｸｿだからじゃない｡
うわぁ それ傷つくなぁ｡
Wow, that hurts.
自信なくして
女性恐怖症になりそう｡
I might lose all confidence and gain a fear of women.
そんなことにはならないわよ｡
その心は？
That won't happen.
What makes you so sure?
上手にできるようになるまで
Because I'll let you practice as many times as you want until you can do it right.
私が 何度でも
練習させてあげるから｡
麻衣さん…｡
何よ？
Mai-san...
What?
すげえ好きです｡
知ってる｡
I love you with all my heart.
I know.
じゃ おやすみ｡
はい おやすみなさい｡
Good night, then.
Yeah. Good night.
August 3rd
Onii-chan, this is yummy! It's so soft!
お兄ちゃん これ おいしいです！
ﾌﾜﾌﾜしてます｡
The egg's great too.
玉子もうまいぞ｡
And this melts in my mouth!
こっちはﾄﾛﾄﾛしてます｡
Let's have Mai-san cook for us
every day from now on.
これから 麻衣さんに
毎日 作ってもらおうな｡
Yeah!
はい！
かえでちゃんを
Don't use Kaede-chan as an excuse.
利用するんじゃないの！
ｲｯ！
What's the matter, Onii-chan?
どうしたんですか？ お兄ちゃん｡
愛を試されてるんだ｡
My love's being put to the test.
You don't like it, Futaba-san?
双葉さん 口に合わない？
あっ いえ
Oh, it's not that.
誰かとの朝食が
久しぶりだったので｡
It's just been a while since the last time
I wasn't alone for breakfast.
Good morning, Sakuta-san.
おはようございます 咲太さん｡
Morning.
おはよう｡
あっ…｡
お客様ですか？
ちょっといろいろあってね｡
Do you have visitors?
It's a long story.
大丈夫だから あがって｡
But don't worry about that. Come on in.
Oh, morning, Shouko-chan.
あっ おはよう 翔子ちゃん｡
おはようございます｡
Good morning.
咲太さんは 女性のお知り合いが
多いんですね｡
You have a lot of female friends, Sakuta-san.
あ…｡
あっ 他意はありません｡
Oh, I didn't mean anything by that.
She's Futaba Rio, a friend from school.
彼女は 双葉理央
高校の同級生｡
牧之原翔子といいます｡
My name is Makinohara Shouko.
She's real, huh?
ﾎﾝﾄに実在したんだ…｡
Futaba, you in?
双葉 いるか？
そういや 国見が
練習試合やってるって言ってたな｡
Come to think of it, Kunimi said he had a practice game.
Suimei U Prep
Minegahara High
There she is.
いるな｡
あれ ３年生かな？
Is that a third-year?
She looks kinda sexy. Sexy and smart.
なんかｴﾛい ｴﾛ賢い｡
Is Kunimi balling out?
国見は活躍してんのか？
I just came to take a peek while I was here for club.
部活のついでに
見に来ただけだから｡
双葉も ｢ｷｬｰ 国見！｣とか
やったら？
Why don't you join the others and go, "Ohmigosh! Kunimi!"?
I'm rooting for him too.
応援ならしてる｡
心の中で？
On the inside?
双葉はｱﾋﾟｰﾙ不足なんだよ｡
邪魔しないでほしいんだけど｡
You're not doing enough to appeal to him.
Could you stop bothering me?
Suimei U Prep
Minegahara High
で 結局 双葉は
国見のどこに惚れたわけ？
Y'know, all said and done,
what about Kunimi made you fall for him?
知ってどうするの？
べつに どうも｡
Why do you want to know?
No reason, really. Just curious.
単なる興味｡
ﾊｧ…｡
Chocolate cornet.
ﾁｮｺｺﾛﾈ｡
ﾀﾞｯｼｭで買ってこいと？
Buy you one on the double?
No.
違う｡
お弁当を持ってこなかった日に
When I didn't bring lunch one day,
Kunimi let me have his.
国見がくれた｡
It was during our first term here.
１年の１学期で
ﾊﾟﾝ販売を利用するのは
That was the first time I'd had to visit the school shop.
あの日が初めてで…｡
I gave up and was walking away when Kunimi talked to me.
圧倒されている私に
国見が声をかけてきた｡
You're a girl, Futaba. You like sweet stuff, don't you?
⦅双葉は女子だから
甘いものが好きだよな⦆
He said that while eating his prized curry bun.
(理央)戦利品のｶﾚｰﾊﾟﾝを
食べながら｡
The Curry Bun Prince, huh?
ｶﾚｰﾊﾟﾝの王子様だな｡
それで？
それだけ｡
And?
That's it.
ﾁｮｺｺﾛﾈって いくら？
130円｡
How much is a chocolate cornet?
130 yen.
Your love doesn't cost much, huh?
双葉って お手軽なのな｡
I wouldn't have fallen for you in that situation.
相手が梓川だったら
好きになってなかった｡
So in the end, it's all about looks?
結局 顔かよ｡
結局 ﾀｲﾐﾝｸﾞだと思う｡
I think it was all about the timing.
I was really down in the dumps back then.
あの頃 気分が落ちてたから｡
If you want to stare, just do it.
見たけりゃ 見ればいいのに｡
A-Anyway, what do you want?
それで 梓川は何の用？
今さ うちに双葉がいるんだよ｡
Futaba's at my place right now.
なるほど 昨日の夜
電話の様子がおかしかったのは
I see. So that's why you sounded off
on the phone last night.
そのせい｡
これって
何が起きてるんだろうな｡
What's going on here?
私のこと 偽者だと思ってる？
Do you think I'm a fake?
正直 最初は そう思ってた｡
Honestly, I did at first.
けど こうして話してると
どっちも双葉だ｡
But after talking to you like this,
I realize you're both Futaba.
What does my other self think?
もう一人の私の見解は？
可能性があるとすれば
量子ﾃﾚﾎﾟｰﾃｰｼｮﾝだとか｡
She said the only thing she could think of
was quantum teleportation.
私と同じ考えだね｡
Same as me, huh?
双葉を観測しているのは
双葉の意識そのもので
You're being observed by
your own consciousness,
その意識がなんらかの理由で
and for some reason, there are two of those, was the assumption.
２つ存在しているんじゃないか
って考察だったな｡
原因については？
心当たりはないってさ｡
What about the cause?
She said she had no idea.
And you believed her lie?
そんなｳｿを梓川は信じたわけ？
なんで ｳｿだと思う？
What makes you think she was lying?
私には心当たりがあるから｡
Because I have a very good idea of what caused it.
If it doesn't matter which one I ask,
why don't you tell me?
どっちに聞いても同じなら
教えてくれ｡
私 部活に戻るから｡
I'm going back to club.
このＸとＹはｶｯｺの中だから…｡
X and Y here are inside the parentheses...
Right.
はい｡
ｺｰﾋｰ淹れるけど 飲む？
I'm making coffee. Want some?
Y-Yes, please.
あっ はい どうも｡
I'm the little sister,
かえでは妹なので
ﾐﾙｸとﾊﾁﾐﾂたっぷりの
so my favorite is café au lait
with lots of milk and honey!
ﾊﾆｰｶﾌｪｵﾚが好きです｡
I'd love to have that as well.
私も かえでちゃんと同じものを
いただけると うれしいです｡
じゃあ 私もそうしようかな｡
[℡]
Maybe I'll go with that too.
あっ ごめん かえでちゃん
ﾏﾈｰｼﾞｬｰからみたい｡
Sorry, Kaede-chan!
Looks like it's my manager.
どうかしたんですか？
[℡]今 お電話は？
Is something the matter?
Are you free to talk?
Sure.
大丈夫です｡
[℡]昨日まで撮影お疲れさまでした｡
Great work with the shoot.
Are you out right now?
[℡]もしかして 今 外ですか？
はい 彼氏の家です｡
Yeah, I'm over at my boyfriend's place.
[℡]あ～ 彼氏… って えっ!?
Oh, your boyfriend...
Wait, boyfriend? Did you just say "boyfriend"?!
[℡]彼氏!?
今 彼氏って言いました？
Wasn't Futaba here until a moment ago?
双葉 さっきまでいたよな｡
気づいてたのかよ｡
You noticed?
Soon after the game started.
試合が始まって すぐ｡
双葉って よく来るのか？
Does she come to watch often?
ん～ どうだろ 科学部のついでに
たまにって感じ？
Hmm, dunno. Feels like she drops by every now and then while she's here for club.
どっちが ついでなんだか｡
もしかして
I wonder which one has higher priority.
Did something happen to her?
双葉に何かあった？
何かって なんだよ？
What do you mean?
咲太は 夏休みに
登校してくるほど
I know you don't like school enough to come in during summer break.
学校が好きじゃないだろ？
となると 双葉に
So I figured maybe something happened to her.
何かあったのかなって｡
≪国見先輩 ｺｰﾁが呼んでます｡
わかった 今行く｡
Kunimi-senpai, the coach wants you.
Gotcha. Coming.
何かあったら 声かけろよ｡
ん？
Let me know if you need anything.
双葉のこと｡
言われなくても そのつもり｡
With Futaba.
I would have anyway. You'd better come flying even if I call you in the dead of night.
夜中に連絡しても飛んで来いよ｡
空は飛べそうにないから
I don't think I can fly for real, so I'll just make my bike fly.
ﾁｬﾘを飛ばして行くわ｡
[℡]はい 梓川です｡
Hello? This is Azusagawa.
Mai-san, could you say that one more time?
麻衣さん それ
もう一度お願いします｡
Hello. This is Azusagawa.
はい 梓川です｡
Could you sound a little more like a newlywed?
[℡]もっと新妻風がいいな｡
I'm amazed you can get so excited over a phone greeting.
電話一本で よくそこまで
はしゃげるわね｡
[℡]そっちは どうだったの？
双葉 学校に来てました｡
How'd it go with you?
Futaba came to school.
そう こっちもずっといるわよ｡
I see. This one's been here the entire time.
Anyway, can you come home now?
[℡]それより もう帰ってこられる？
どうかしたんですか？
Is something the matter?
[℡]さっきﾏﾈｰｼﾞｬｰから電話があって
ちょっとね｡
My manager called me earlier.
I need to talk to you about something.
[℡]咲太に話したいことがあるの｡
僕に？
To me?
なに？
[℡]いえ なんでも｡
What's up?
Nothing. I'll talk to you later.
[℡]それじゃ あとで｡
You're friends with that girl, aren't you?
(沙紀)梓川って あの女と
友達なのよね？
あの女というのは 察するに
双葉のことか？
I suppose you're talking about Futaba.
Isn't she up to some pretty funny business?
なんかﾔﾊﾞいことしてない？
あの女｡
ﾔﾊﾞいこと？
これ
Funny business?
Here. Look at her secret account.
あの女の裏ｱｶ｡
Selfie 72
Selfie 71
Selfie 70
Selfie 69
That's my Onii-chan! A total pig!
Next Episode
#8: Let the Rain Wash Everything Anew